

// ############################################## SITE SETTINGS ##############################################

// ############################################## SITE SETTINGS ##############################################

export const SITE_TITLE = "Savari Dekho";

export const USER = "User";
export const RIDER = "Rider";
export const ROLES = {
  USER,
  RIDER
};

// ############################################## RESPONSE TYPES ##############################################

export const RES = {
  ERROR: 'error',
  SUCCESS: 'success',
};

// ############################################## UI Constants ##############################################

export const DRAWER_WIDTH = 280;
export const APP_BAR_MOBILE = 64;
export const APP_BAR_DESKTOP = 92;

export const THEME = {
  LIGHT: "Light",
  DARK: "Dark",
};

// ############################################## FAQS ##############################################

export const WALLET_FAQS = [
  {
    question: "Q: What is the Quantum Quill?",
    answer: "A: The Quantum Quill is a state-of-the-art, time-traveling pen designed for the adventurous writers of tomorrow. It allows you to pen stories from any era, past or future!"
  },
  {
    question: "Q: How does the Quantum Quill work?",
    answer: "A: The Quantum Quill utilizes a combination of nano-scribbler technology and quantum entanglement. Just think of the time and place you want to write about, press the nib to paper, and let your imagination flow!"
  },
  {
    question: "Q: Is the Quantum Quill safe to use?",
    answer: "A: Absolutely! The Quantum Quill has been rigorously tested and comes with built-in safety measures to prevent any unintended paradoxes or reality disruptions. However, we recommend not using it for winning lottery numbers."
  },
  {
    question: "Q: Can I write myself into the past or future with the Quantum Quill?",
    answer: "A: While the Quantum Quill is great for fictional adventures, it cannot alter real history or transport you physically through time. Its magic is confined to the realms of fiction."
  },
  {
    question: "Q: Can I use the Quantum Quill as a regular pen?",
    answer: "A: Of course! The Quantum Quill comes with a switch to toggle between time-traveling mode and regular ink mode. You can jot down your grocery list or draft your novel all in one device."
  },
  {
    question: "Q: How many words can the Quantum Quill write before it runs out of ink?",
    answer: "A: The Quantum Quill employs quantum nano-ink technology, so you'll never run out of ink! It's a pen that writes endlessly, just like your imagination."
  },
  // {
  //   question: "Q: Can the Quantum Quill be used for non-fiction writing?",
  //   answer: "A: While the Quantum Quill is primarily designed for creative writing, it can also be used for non-fiction. Just remember to stay within the bounds of reality if you're not looking for an adventure."
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "Q: What happens if I lose my Quantum Quill?",
  //   answer: "A: Losing your Quantum Quill is not just losing a writing tool; it's losing a potential portal to countless worlds. Always keep it safe and treat it like the treasure it is!"
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "Q: Can I share my Quantum Quill adventures with others?",
  //   answer: "A: Absolutely! The Quantum Quill comes with an integrated storytelling platform where you can share your fantastical tales with a community of fellow adventurers."
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "Q: Can I collaborate with other writers using the Quantum Quill?",
  //   answer: "A: Yes, indeed! The Quantum Quill allows collaborative writing through the wonders of quantum synchronization. Team up with friends or even your future self for truly epic tales."
  // }
];
